

# **ALICIA MORALES**

**COMPUTER SCIENCE FNGINFFR** 

#### **ADDRESS:**

Hospitalet de Llobregat 08904



## PHONE:

+34 665 37 07 08



#### **EMAIL:**

alicia5324@gmail.com



## SKYPE:

alice2360



## **DATE OF BIRTH:**

24 February 1995



## **WEBSITE:**

aliciamorales.ml

# **SKILLS**

**JAVA** 

**SCALA** 

**PYTHON** 

C

# SOCIAL



github.com/amoralca16



twitter.com/amoralca16



linkedin.com/in/aliciamorales-carrasco-81a3ba8

# PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Graduate of Computer Science Engineering at Universitat de Barcelona with in-depth knowledge in programming and a great interest in Big Data and Artificial Intelligence.

Comprehensive understanding on database software, experience with Agile methodologies and good English oral and writen communication skills.

"I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." - Thomas A. Edison

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Universitat de Barcelona

MACHINE LEARNING Completed a course on Statistical and Machine Learning where I could learn and practise the fundamentals of ML and Deep Learning with R.

**GAME DEVELOPER** 

2016-2017

Made two game development projects with Unity and C#, one with a team of twenty people and another one in a hackathon. Both were the winners of their respective contests.

**WEB DEVELOPER** 

2016-2017

Created a flight purchasing site using RESTful, Django and Javascript.

# **EDUCATION**

**BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE** 

2013-2018

Universitat de Barcelona

Specialized on Distributed Artificial Intelligence, Distributed Software, Machine Learning and Data Mining. Mark: 8.03

**TECH BATXILLERAT** Graduated with honors, PAU June 2013. Mark: 9.01

2011-2013

INS Vicenc Plantada

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **BIG DATA ENGINEER**

SCRM Lidl Digital

Designed and developed the Lidl international analytics data platform.

10.2018 - Present

- Modeled data sources - Did Spark Scala ETLs
- Designed Databricks metastore
- Supported Business Intelligence non-normalized layer
- Orchestrated Spark jobs, integrated CI/CD pipelines and more.

#### COMPUTER VISION

02.2018 - 06.2018 colorSensing

Developed an image processing and computer vision software for the quantitative analysis of test strips.

## **BIG DATA INTERN**

10.2017 - 01.2018 Everis Spain, S.L.U. Supported the development of Big Data projects doing testing, preparing documentation and suggesting improvements. Worked with Big Data Architecture: Spark, Hadoop, Scala, AWS, Azure...

2017 - 2018

Universitat de Barcelona

PROFESSOR ASSISTANT Lectured, designed assignments and helped in programming and data structures subjects.